<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Before 2022 | Welcome!</title>
    <link>https://leodong.github.io/tags/before-2022/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://leodong.github.io/tags/before-2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Before 2022</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://leodong.github.io/images/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Before 2022</title>
      <link>https://leodong.github.io/tags/before-2022/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Functional Analysis of Drosophila TCTP Regulating Immune SignalingPathway to Enhance Cell Tolerance to Deltamethrin</title>
      <link>https://leodong.github.io/project/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://leodong.github.io/project/5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;B.Sc. Graduation Project&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Supervisor: Prof. &lt;em&gt;Luogen Cheng&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Translationally controlled tumor protein(TCTP) is a multifunctional protein that is highly conserved in a variety of species. TCTP expression is highly regulated and affects many life processes such as cell growth and differentiation. Since the expression of TCTP was upregulated in drug-resistant insects, we analyzed the effect of TCTP on the expression of drsl1, a gene downstream of the Toll-like receptor signaling pathway, to investigate the regulatory role of TCTP on cellular tolerance. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Studying the relationship between resistance of Drosophila cells to Deltamethrin and TCTP expression &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Overexpression and interference of TCTP gene in Drosophila cells &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyzing the changes of TCTP expression levels in cells and their effects on gene drsl1 by qPCR &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screening and Identification of Soil Fungi Carrying Soybean Mosaic Virus</title>
      <link>https://leodong.github.io/project/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://leodong.github.io/project/6/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;&lt;strong&gt;2019 Provincial Key (National) College Student Innovation and Entrepreneurship Training Program&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Supervisor: Prof. &lt;em&gt;Kai Xu&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Current research shows the main transmission mode of SMV is seed transmission and aphid transmission，but soil fungi are an important way for plant viruses to spread. Since soybean mosaic disease tends to strike in a certain region year after year, soil fungi are likely to be the mediators of SMV and cause soybean mosaic disease. We attempted to screen for fungi capable of carrying SMV to provide new perspectives on the control of soybean mosaic disease. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cultivating model plants and inoculating Soybean Mosaic Viruses &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Isolating and purifying soil fungi &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Screening out the fungi suspected of carrying SMV &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
